<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<entry>
		<name>General Edward A. Rice Jr.</name>
		<headerHTML><![CDATA[<div id="headerTxt"><h1>It's not where you come from;<br />it's what you want to become.</h1><p>They come from different backgrounds and with different experiences.<br />They are doctors, engineers, lawyers and EOD techs. And while they share<br />a common mission, they are anything but common. These are the stories<br />of America's Airmen who make up the U.S. Air Force.</p><img src="img/amair_headerThumb_generalRice.jpg" /><div id="headerCTA"><p>Watch the introduction <br />by General Edward A. Rice Jr.<br /><a class="CTAbtn" href="javascript:void(0);" rel="address:/general_edward_rice">Play Video</a></p></div></div>]]></headerHTML>
		<bgImg altText="Thumbnail image alt text">img/amair_header.jpg</bgImg>
		<pagePath>general_edward_rice</pagePath>
		<imgPath>img/amair_thumb_rice.jpg</imgPath>
		<vidPath>../vids/airmanFPO.mp4</vidPath>
		<posterPath>img/amair_FPO_poster.jpg</posterPath>
		<hometown>Mexico City, MX</hometown>
		<currentDuty>Davis-Monthan AFB, AZ</currentDuty>
		<jobTitle>Foreign Policy Advisor to the Commander, 12th Air Force</jobTitle>
		<jobDescription><![CDATA[Serves as Foreign Policy Advisor providing expert foreign policy, political-military, economic and strategic nonmilitary advice and information relevant to command activities and responsibilities.]]></jobDescription>
		<careerHighlights><![CDATA[AC-130 Navigator 1994; AC-130H Instructor Navigator 1996; Chief, Wing Flight Safety 2003; Air Force Section Chief, US Embassy Guatemala, 2005; Air Coordinator, Hurricane Stan Relief Operations, 2005; Air Force Mission Chief, US Embassy Ecuador, 2007]]></careerHighlights>
		<background><![CDATA[Born and raised in Mexico, from an American father and a Mexican mother,  Lt Col Ferraro and his five siblings were home schooled so they could learn English. His love affair with flying began as a boy when he saw the Thunderbirds perform at an air show in the U.S. After working his way through college at Arizona University and joining AFROTC at Embry-Riddle Aernautical University, Lt Col Ferraro earned a Bachelor’s degree in Computer  Science and was commissioned as a 2nd Lieutenant in the U.S. Air Force.]]></background>
		<trackingURL>http://view.atdmt.com/action/astbrl_Videos_1</trackingURL>
	</entry>
</data>